# MEHDI ABBASZADE

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### **DETAILS**

Stackoverflow

**Address Phone** 

+98 930 109 8945 Iran, Tehran

https://stackoverflow.com/users/13975606/mttinor

**Email** 

mttinor@yahoo.com

Skype

live:mttinor\_1

LinkedIn

Github www.linkedin.com/in/mttinor

https://github.com/mttinor1

# **PROFILE**

I'm Mehdi Abbaszadeh I started work as a front developer in 2017 I have 4 years experience i developing responsive web application, skilled in JavaScript, ReactJS, NodeJS, VueJs Always creative, eager to learn and Teamwork Interested in problemsolving and developing complex web applications.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Fronend developer

Jan 2021 - Present

Skills: Docker · TypeScript · JavaScript · Vue.js · React.js

Fronend developer

Middle East Bank Brokerage · Full-time

Jan 2019 - Mar 2021

RASA (Iranian Human Capital Development) · Full-time

Skills: boostrap vue · JavaScript · Vue.js

During my tenure as a front-end developer in this company, I have created various projects to meet internal company needs. We utilized Vue and React frameworks in different projects. One of my primary challenges in this company was integrating and collaborating with three different WebSocket services used to provide real-time market data to internal users. This challenge was crucial as it required synchronizing and coordinating real-time information with other services, enabling users to make more informed decisions in their transactions. To manage the state of this data and implement a standardized management system, we employed state management solutions. This not only improved the overall project performance but also allowed us to optimally utilize the received data across the project, ensuring the best use of data throughout the entire project.

Fronend developer

Jan 2019 - Dec 2019

Sayan Business · Full-time

Skills: HTML5 · Bootstrap · css3

- Design of store and personal websites using CSS and HTML, as well as Bootstrap4.
- · Vue.js has been used for implementing projects
- In this company, dynamic forms were designed to create dynamic parameters by sending keywords. These forms could be sent to the back-end, and the response of the filter could be seen in real-time. Components were designed to dynamically apply the filters to each page, and the problem was solved by implementing dynamic forms in this way.

## **EDUCATION**

## **University of Qom**

Amirkabir University of Technology - Tehran Polytechnic

Bachelor's Degree in economic Sep 2015 - Dec 2018

Master's Degree in Information technology Oct 2021 - Oct 2023

#### SKILLS

- · React.js Javascript Jquery TypeScript · Node.js Vue.js
- Docker · Css · Less and sass · Html5 RestFull Api · Fetch & Axios Bootsrap

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Persian

_			